Guide to the Clive L. DuVal papers, 1960-1994
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Legislative Files, 1966-1992
  - Subseries 2.1 - Congressional Bills, 1966-1992; (68 Boxes)
    - Bond Issue, SB785, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - AG Change in Building Code Re: Energy Conservation, SB803, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - AG Definition of Rate Classifications in Insurance Policies, SB804, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Veterans' Children - Tuition Exemption, SB805, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Nom. Commission (SCC), SB806, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Property Exemption from Taxation, SJR042, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Auctioneer Study, SJR092, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Study of Safety, etc. of Nuclear Power Plants, SJR136, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Spouse Abuse, SJR89, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Amendment to Budget Bill, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Carry Over Bills, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Nuclear Report, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Staunton-Scenic River HB0154, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - (Guest) Parimutuel Betting on Horse Racing, HB0204, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - General Elections in Virginia, HJR008, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Maurice, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Accelerated Sales Tax Repeal, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - School Buses, SB116, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - Pipeline Safety, SB161, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Fuel Adjustment Clause Profit, SB162, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Fuel Adjustment Clause by Public Utilities, SB188, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Bottle Bill, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Attorney General-Rate Classif. Statement Carry Over Bill, SB201, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Attorney General Consumer Bill of Rights, Amended, SB202, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Certification of Desirability, E. M. Miller, SB260, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Certification, SB260, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Purchase of Service Credit, SB261, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Handicapped Persons Exemption from Sales Tax for Optional Equipment on..., SB349, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Exemption for Equipment on Cops Handicapped, SB349, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Rates of Public Utilities by SCC, SB375, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Council for the Deaf (Old Number), SB383, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Emergency Evacuation Plans, SB537, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Negotiation with Public Employer, SB537, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - ERA, SJR014, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Holding Tax Resolution, SJR024, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Holding Tanks Subcommittee, SJR024, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - DC Voting Rights Amendment, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - DuVal Bills, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - GMU ISL [International School of Law, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Legislation for 1979 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Car, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Study of Granting Localities the Option of Offering Veterans a One Time Preference in Hiring, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Vendorship for Virginia Social Workers, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Optometrists Nuclear Power, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Optometric Use of Diagnostic Drugs (pt 1), HB1262, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Optometrists Use of Diagnostic Drugs (pt 2), HB1262, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Farm Credit, HB1678, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Accelerated Sales Tax, SB089; SB090, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Commissioner in Chancery, SB117, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Pipeline Safety, SB161, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Underground Utility Damage Prevention Act, SB161, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Fuel Adjustment Clause Profit, SB162, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Auto Rate Classifications, SB201, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Public Utility Consumer Rights, SB202, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - VSRS (5% Purchase Plan) E. M. Miller, SB261, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Social Workers carried over to 1979 Session, SB348 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Council for the Deaf, SB383, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Coastal Management, SB403, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Falls Church Charter Bill, SB621, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Definition of "Special Equipment" on Auto for Handicapped Drivers, SB728, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - American Flag Tax Exemption, SB729, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Immunity from Liability, SB772, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Immunity of Prescribing Physician, SB772, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Exemption for Special Equipment for Handicapped, SB778, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Charitable Solicitations, Solicitation of Contributions Act, SB839, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Solicitation of Contributions Act (pt 1), SB839, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Solicitation of Contributions Act (pt 2), SB839, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Gas and Electricity Cut-Off, SB883, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Prohibition against Winter Cut-Off of Gas or Electricity, SB883, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Consumer Counsel (79 Expenses of Office of AG), SB884, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - VEPCO Payment of AG Expenses, SB884, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Temporary Rate Increase Limitations, SB885, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Abortion, SB927, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Judge Retirement, SJR002, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ERA Material carried over to 1979, SJR014 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Limits on State Spending, SJR109, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Limitation on State Spending (Constitutional Amendment), SJR109, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Holding Tank Study - Extension, SJR110, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Initiation Referendum, SJR115, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - John S. Mosby Highway (pt 1), SJR168, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - John S. Mosby Highway (pt 2), SJR168, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Bicycles, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Credit for Solar Star, Etc. Priddy, Sumpter Resolution, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Interest on Escrow Funds, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Limitation of State Expenses, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Priddy, Sumpter T., Jr., 1980 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Trucks-Taxation, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Women's Property Rights, 1980 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - (1) Dunes Protection, (2) Wetlands Expansion - Mudland (pt 1), HB0204-206; SB222-241, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - (1) Dunes Protection, (2) Wetlands Expansion - Mudland (pt 2), HB0204-206; SB222-241, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - (1) Dunes Protection, (2) Wetlands Expansion - Mudland (pt 3), HB0204-206; SB222-241, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - SCC Expansion of Members from 3 to 5 (Dick Bagley's Bill), HB0683, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - VEPCO Bill, HB0861, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Sales Tax on Food, Study on Replacing Lost Revenue if Repealed (pt 1), HJR0197, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Sales Tax on Food, Study on Replacing Lost Revenue if Repealed (pt 2), HJR0197, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - ERA, SB027, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Marriage Records, Elimination of References to "Race," SB053, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Marriage License Charges, SB053, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Increase Travel Expenses, SB105, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Marriage Licenses, Authorizing Certain Persons to Issue, SB124, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Marriage Licenses, SB124, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Hang Gliding (pt 1), SB212, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Hang Gliding (pt 2), SB212, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Grantois Tax (Increase) [carried over 1981], SB219, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Condominium Conversion, Notice to Tenants, SB265, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Amendments to SB161; SB289, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Underground Utility Damage Prevention Act, SB289, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Boards of Zoning Appeals, SB343, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Board of Zoning Appeals Appointment by Fairfax Board, SB343, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Nuclear Evacuation Plans, SB344, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Study of Littel River Turnpike, SJR168; Mosby-Rte 50, SB351, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Shoplifting (pt 1), SB360, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Shoplifting (pt 2), SB360, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Dunes Protection, SB362, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Condominium Board Review of Condo Conversion (pt 1), SB471, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Condominium Board Review of Condo Conversion (pt 2), SB471, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Storage Site for Radioactive Materials, SB473, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (pt 1), SJR027, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (pt 2), SJR027, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - ERA in P and E 9-6, Limitations of State Expenses (pt 1), SJR027, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - ERA in P and E 9-6, Limitations of State Expenses (pt 2), SJR027, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - ERA in P and E 9-6, Limitations of State Expenses (pt 3), SJR027, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - ERA in P and E 9-6, Limitations of State Expenses (pt 4), SJR027, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Holding Tank Resolution, SJR035, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Abortion Survey, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Acid Rain, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, Evaluation Committee, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Coastal Management, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Comparable Worth, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Conservation Restrictions Act-Study of Former HB1189, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Minister-Paulus, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Patron's Weekly Report, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Shelter Workshop, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Reimbursement-Expenses Incurred on State Business, SB105, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Condo-Conservation Notification Passed, SB265, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Evacuation Plans Re: Nuclear (Passed), SB265, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Radioactive Waste Material carried over to 1981, SB473 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County-Road Improvement by County, SB660, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Hazardous Waste-Penalties for Illegal Transportation, SB704, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Recycled Paper, SB704, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Homeowners Exemption from Real Property Taxes carried over to 1981, SJR013; SJR015 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Homestead Exemption Amendment of 1980 carried over to 1981, SJR015 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Farm Credit Passed, SJR049, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Public Utilities, Study of Role in Encouraging Energy Conservation, File 1, SJR155, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Public Utilities, Study of Role in Encouraging Energy Conservation, File 2, SJR155, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Public Utilities, Study of Role in Encouraging Energy Conservation, File 3, SJR155, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Annual Auto Inspection, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Architects/Engineers License Law Changes and Harry Adreon, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Arlington County Government, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Beverage Container Current (pt 1), 1982 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Beverage Container Current (pt 2), 1982 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Bills, Resolutions, etc. Cosponsored by Clive DuVal, 2nd, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Claims Bills - House and Senate, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - CLD Legislation, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Coal Mine Reclamation 2 Acres Exception, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Coal Bills Portsmouth, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Commercial Practice of Optometry, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Credit Card Interest Rates, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - ERA (pt 1), 1982 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - ERA (pt 2), 1982 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - ERA (pt 3), 1980-1982 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fire Alarm System at Staunton School, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Funding Kindergarten, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - George Mason NOVA Community College, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Gun Control, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - House Claims Bills, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Housing Legislation, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Joannou Tax Bill, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - John S. Mosby Highway, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Long Term Care for Elderly Virginians, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Metro Facts and Figures, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Northern Virginia Airport Authority, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Prohibiting Posting of Signs on Right of Way, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Public Education: Additional Funds, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Recycling of Oil, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Registered Lobbyists, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Senate Bills Co-Sponsored by Senator DuVal, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Senate Finance Northern Virginia Faculty, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Senate Finance Subcommittee on Health and Human Services, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Study on Relocating of Toxic Wastes, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Television Sessions, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Time Share Sales Legislation and Info., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Trucks Don't Pay Enough Taxes, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Uranium Mining, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Veteran's Cemetery, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Energy Publication, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Patron's Report, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Withholding Legislation, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Women's Issues, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Statement on House Bill 1664; Legislation Governing the University Extension, HB1664, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Medicaid Funding for Abortion, HB1571; HB1577, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Sales Tax off Food, HB1715, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Pesticide Law Amendment, Prohibiting Posting of Signs on ROW [Rights of Way], SB090, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Pesticide Registration, SB090, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Am Ve Flag-sales, SB155, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Flags, SB155, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Mosby Highway (pt 1), SB156, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Mosby Highway (pt 2), SB156, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Consolidated Housing Authority (Arlington), SB177, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Consolidated Housing Authorities, SB177, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Exemption from Taxation - Fairfax County Vocational Education Foundation, SB178, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Wetlands Unvegetated, HB389, HB390, and HB400; Grayson, HB400, SB238, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Wetlands Refiation Produce of Boards, SB238, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - To Authorize "Mini Agriculture of Forest Districts," SB255, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Sales Tax off Food, SB257, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Sexual Assault, SB258, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Commissioner of Revenue, Power to Summons (Arlington), SB304, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Commissioner of Revenue Subpoena Businesses Failing to Pay License Tax, SB304, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Instruction (Grades 2-6), SB354, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Drug and Alcohol Abuse Instruction, SB354, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Agriculture-Forest "Mini-Districts," SB355, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Truancy Bill (pt 1), SB364, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Truancy Bill (pt 2), SB364, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Generic Drug Substitute, SB469, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Gas Credit Card Bill, SB501, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Falls Church Charter Change, SB616, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Arlington Sanitary District (New Recycling Plant), SB636, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Authorization of Fairfax County to Improve Its Sec. Road, SB660, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Conservation Restrictions, SB683, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Withholding Income Tax Law Amendment, SB703, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Local Government Can Make Loans to Tenants for Down-Payments, SB705, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Local Government Can Use Funds for Loans to Apartment House Owners, SB706, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Recycle Paper, SB740, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Rule 36, HR3, SR004, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Holding Tank Resolution, SJR011, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Holding Tank Study Extension, SJR011, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Commission on Alcohol-Drug-Related Motor, SJR025, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Driving While Under the Influence, SJR025, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - ERA, SJR050, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Comprehensive Drug Control Plan in Each School System, SJR064, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Local School Division Policy for Drug Related Problems, SJR064, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Holding Tank Study, SJR119, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Recycling Used Motor Oil Study, SJR154, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Arlington, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Bills Cosponsored by Senator DuVal, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Claims Bill, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - CLD "Green Space" Bond Issue, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Conflicts of Interests, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Drinking Age 21, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Drunk Driving / Paraphernalia Proposed, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County and School, 1983 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Falls Church Legislation Proposals, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Guilty but Mentally Ill (Insanity), 1983 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - "Infant Doe,", 1983 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Insanity Defense Plea, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Judgeships, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Larry Hoffheimer, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Removal of Sales Tax from Food, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Signs, Unauthorized (Ware), 1983 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Uranium Mining - Marline, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Virginia State Cemetery - Commander of Disabled Veterans, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Wesley, Development Corporation Exemption for Property, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Westwood Racket Club, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - William O'Neill, Jr. Industrial Commission, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Beverage Containers - Current, SB015, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture District Bill - Fairfax Amendment, SB153, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Mini Agriculture Districts, SB153, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Unauthorized Highway, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Flow-Thru Marine Sanitation Devices, SJR006, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Holding Tanks, SJR022, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Dillon's Rule (pt 1), SJR027, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Dillon's Rule (pt 2), 1983 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Toxic Substances, SJR029, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Initiative Referendum Unfolding Material, SJR066, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Initiation (Constitutional Amendment 1979), SJR115, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Beverage Containers, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Chewning Procurement Request, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Claims Subcommittee General Information Claims Bills, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Coal Slurry Pipeline, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Complaint for Mrs. Massi of Arlington Re: Unnecessary Estate Expenditures, Red Tape, etc., 1984 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Drunk Driving, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Escrow Payment for Taxes and Insurance (Daniel L. Benson), 1984 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax County Incl. roads, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Falls Church, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - GMU and NOVA, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Human Resources Committee, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Land Sales, Deceptive Practices (Seaside Properties), 1984 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Legislation - Vienna, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Limitation on State Spending, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Lottery (pt 1), 1984 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Lottery (pt 2), 1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Northern Virginia Delegation, 1984-1986 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Optional Negotiations, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Senate Finance Committee Metro, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Transportation, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - "Trash" Bills (Fairfax County), 1984 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Patron Reports, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Virginia National Guard Income Tax Exemption, HB0010, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Licensing Insurance Agents CLD Chairs, HB0136, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Chairman's File, HB0233, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Chairman's File (OK Cash), HB0251, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Chairman's File (Meier), HB0285, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Chairman's File (Chesapeake), HB0565, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Chairman's File (Fire Bomb), HB0697, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Chairman's File (OK), HB0831, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - CHairman's File: ERA, HB0835, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - VSRS Changes, 1984 Picket (Big James), HB0988 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Animal Wardens, SB074, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Pesticide Operators Penalties for Violation, SB082, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Pesticide Operators Financial Responsibility (Government Request), SB083, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Northern Virginia Construction Dist., SB141, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Head Injuries Registry, SB142, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Chairman's File (Lester), SB152, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Lobbyist Fees Increase, SB165, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Ordinances Tracking State Law (Falls Church), SB195, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - VSRS Contribution - Employer May Pay a Part of Employer Contributions, SB242, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Military Retirement Pay, Division for Support Purposes, SB257, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Motor Vehicle Emmissions, SB259, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Notice of Criminal Costs to PBI, SB268, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Blue Laws - Virginia Beach Charge, SB269, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Chairman's File Acquadro, SB273, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Chairman's File (Troubletz Koy), SB307, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Chairman's File (State Compensation Board), SB310, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Computer Crime (Courts of Justice), SB347, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Garnishment - Continuing - Korman, SB357, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Waver of Int. Taxes Delay to (optimal staff) Goode, SB358, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Chairman's File (Snead), SB365, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Condemnation - Cable TV - Fairfax by Request (Green Box Problem), SB367, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Potomac School of Law (Cts of Justice), SB368, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Automobile Liability Insurance Potter, SB370, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Chairman's File (Carter Escheat Case), SB394, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Rule 36, SR004, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Abortion - Women's Rights, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Alzheimer's Disease (Network Regional Centers), 1985 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Asbestos, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Asbestos Problem, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Bank Fees and Practices, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Beverage Container Legislation Studies, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - C and P Local Measured Service, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Coal Slurry, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Desalinization Study Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - George Mason University - Doctoral Nursing, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - House Bills: Claims Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Legislation (Falls Church), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Legislation George Mason University, NOVA, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - School Board, Fairfax County, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Senate Bills: Claims Subcommittee, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - State Office of Consumer Affairs (Northern Virginia Office), 1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Trucks - Twin Trailers, etc., 1985 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Uranium Mining, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Paint Law, Repeal of, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Withholding Changes, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Road Formula Changes - Manning (pt 1), HB1269, 1985 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Road Formula Changes - Manning (pt 2), HB1269, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Free Tuition, Children of Disabled Veterans, SB482, 1985 (Box 62, Folder 2)